Hello everyone! Hello!
Hej allihopa! Hallå!
I sit and work.
Jag sitter och jobbar.
It's my computer.
Det är min dator.
a computer - my computer The
en dator - min dator
phone rings.
Telefonen ringer.
Who is calling?
Vem är det som ringer?
Hi Anastasia! It's Marie!
Hej Anastasia! Det är Marie!
Hi Marie, that was a long time ago!
Hej Marie, det var längesen!
Yes it was. How are you? How is the family?
Ja, det var det. Hur mår du? Hur mår familjen?
We are fine. How are you? Are all healthy?
Vi mår bra. Hur mår ni? Är alla friska?
Yes, we're fine too.
Ja, vi mår också bra.
I want to wish you and your family a very Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
Jag vill önska dig och din familjen riktigt God jul och ett Gott nytt år!
Thank you Marie, the same!
Tack snälla Marie, detsamma!
Merry Christmas and a Happy New Year!
God jul och Gott nytt år!
Thanks Anastasia! Greet the family!
Tack Anastasia! Hälsa familjen!
Greet your family! Bye!
Hälsa din familj! Hej då!
Bye!
Hej då!
It was Marie, my friend.
Det var Marie, min kompis.
She is also a teacher of Swedish as a second language.
Hon är också lärare i svenska som andraspråk.
She also has a channel on YouTube.
Hon har också en kanal på YouTube.
Go in and have a look!
Gå in och kika!
There are many videos there, many, many.
Det finns många videor där, många-många.
How funny that she called! Great fun!
Vad roligt att hon har ringt! Jättekul!
Really!
Verkligen!
But I have to keep working.
Men jag måste fortsätta jobba.
Thanks for watching!
Tack för att du har tittat!
Feel free to visit Marie's channel. Hope you like it.
Besök gärna Maries kanal. Hoppas att du gillar den.
See you in the next video, hello then!
Vi ses i nästa video, hej då!